<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Philosophy on j.m. kettle</title><link>http://localhost:1314/writing_categories/philosophy/</link><description>Recent content in Philosophy on j.m. kettle</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 11:23:36 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1314/writing_categories/philosophy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Just do it</title><link>http://localhost:1314/writing/do-things/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 11:23:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1314/writing/do-things/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;If there&amp;rsquo;s one piece of advice I would give to anyone, it would be this: just do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Modern life has turned most of us into pure consumers. We&amp;rsquo;re on an IV drip of content, constantly scrolling and waiting for the next thing to show up on our screens. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t always like this, but years of optimization have made our phones possibly the most addictive things in the world. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a cure for this phenomenon: you just have to do it.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>24 Years - Some Reflections</title><link>http://localhost:1314/writing/24-years/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 11:23:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1314/writing/24-years/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I turned 24 this Sunday and it was a crazy, wonderful, and joyous time in Tbilisi with friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For most of my life there was a mismatch of my perceived age and my biological age. When I was a teenager, I always felt that I was older. Then when covid hit, I felt that I had lost 2 years and that I was younger than I actually was. So I wasn&amp;rsquo;t 23, but 21, and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t graduating but just starting junior year. However, time is unsentimental and hardworking, and I was in fact 23 and I did, in fact, graduate. However, after my time in Georgia, I finally feel my actual age. It&amp;rsquo;s as if two gears lined up just perfectly. My early 20s was wrapped up with great friends, loud music, and spectacular food. Now I am ready to continue the march in my life and build something that I and the people that supported me will be proud of.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>