<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Writing on j.m. kettle</title><link>http://localhost:1313/writing/</link><description>Recent content in Writing on j.m. kettle</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 11:23:36 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contra AirPods</title><link>http://localhost:1313/writing/airpods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 11:23:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/airpods/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s September 2025, and reviews are in for the new AirPods 3. They are receiving nearly universal acclaim. There is no doubt that technologically, the AirPods are a marvel. It&amp;rsquo;s been 11 years since the first bluetooth wireless earphones came out, the Bragi Dash, and 10 years since the first AirPods arrived to consumers. Over the decade, they have made significant improvements, most notably with the AirPod Pros&amp;rsquo; noise cancelling feature. Now, in 2025, we have reached near perfection. The question remains, have AirPods made our world better? Are we more connected and happier, or more isolated and locked in our digital worlds?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>100 Haikus</title><link>http://localhost:1313/writing/100-haikus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 11:23:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/100-haikus/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This summer I wrote a haiku every day and put it on my personal website. The rules were simple: each poem had to have the classic 5-7-5 structure, and I had to write only one per day. There were no other rules. Haikus have a long and beautiful tradition in Japanese literary history, I decided to ignore it, because the goal was simply to write one a day about my life. I didn&amp;rsquo;t announce this goal publicly; it just happened naturally. The project took on a life of its own and has become one of my favorite works. Here are a few of my favorites:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Daily Haiku</title><link>http://localhost:1313/writing/daily-haikus/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 11:23:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/daily-haikus/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;October 1, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Founder on speed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am grateful for my life&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beers, dinner with friends&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;September 30, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;working in Brooklyn&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;maybe i don’t need a job&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;wine on balcony&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;September 29, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lonely day inside&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Magical beers with my friends&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;life is that simple&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;September 28, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can’t get out of bed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Long walk by the pier with friend&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goodbye Safia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;September 27, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Late nights and long rides&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Things I Love</title><link>http://localhost:1313/writing/i-love/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 11:23:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/i-love/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Things I love:&lt;br&gt;
Techno&lt;br&gt;
The French language&lt;br&gt;
Snails and raw beef&lt;br&gt;
Coffee&lt;br&gt;
Cigarettes&lt;br&gt;
The feeling of the sun on your face as you are submerged in water&lt;br&gt;
70% dark chocolate&lt;br&gt;
Georgia (country)&lt;br&gt;
Hugs from old friends&lt;br&gt;
Dancing in a good club&lt;br&gt;
Reading a good book&lt;br&gt;
Writing a good article&lt;br&gt;
Taking a good picture&lt;br&gt;
The Moma&lt;br&gt;
Sand&lt;br&gt;
Funny stories&lt;br&gt;
Wine&lt;br&gt;
Well designed apartments&lt;br&gt;
Beautiful buildings&lt;br&gt;
My family&lt;br&gt;
Levi’s 550s (38,34)&lt;br&gt;
Running 3 miles&lt;br&gt;
Sardines on toast&lt;br&gt;
Bagels&lt;br&gt;
French people who don’t speak English and refuse to learn&lt;br&gt;
Political debates with open minded people
Love&lt;br&gt;
Running my hand through someone’s hair&lt;br&gt;
My Subaru with no technology in it&lt;br&gt;
Vinyl records&lt;br&gt;
Real books&lt;br&gt;
Hailing taxis&lt;br&gt;
College libraries&lt;br&gt;
Parties&lt;br&gt;
Raves&lt;br&gt;
Dinners with 5+ more friends&lt;br&gt;
The lower east side&lt;br&gt;
The upper west side&lt;br&gt;
Brooklyn&lt;br&gt;
Food in California&lt;br&gt;
The beach&lt;br&gt;
Skiing&lt;br&gt;
Swimming in the Ocean&lt;br&gt;
Jumping into lakes&lt;br&gt;
Old friends&lt;br&gt;
Becoming friends with someone randomly&lt;br&gt;
Brazilians&lt;br&gt;
Hanging with someone smarter than you but who still meets you at your level&lt;br&gt;
Beautiful people&lt;br&gt;
Braces/Invisalign&lt;br&gt;
Cleaning my skin&lt;br&gt;
Using sunscreen&lt;br&gt;
Cowboy boots&lt;br&gt;
Olive oil&lt;br&gt;
Sparkling water&lt;br&gt;
People who are fit but not like too into it&lt;br&gt;
Print Magazines&lt;br&gt;
Meeting people not on dating apps&lt;br&gt;
Wine dates&lt;br&gt;
The F train&lt;br&gt;
Citi bikes&lt;br&gt;
Berlin&lt;br&gt;
Tbilisi&lt;br&gt;
Marseille&lt;br&gt;
Paris&lt;br&gt;
Dogs&lt;br&gt;
Cameras&lt;br&gt;
SoundCloud&lt;br&gt;
BBQs&lt;br&gt;
Doing push-ups&lt;br&gt;
Earnest blog posts&lt;br&gt;
Real people&lt;br&gt;
People who don’t take themselves to seriously&lt;br&gt;
Sympathy&lt;br&gt;
Extraversion&lt;br&gt;
Forgiveness&lt;br&gt;
Moments of ecstasy&lt;br&gt;
Knowing a dinner will be the last time you’ll see the person so you take time to enjoy it&lt;br&gt;
Special ceremonies&lt;br&gt;
Weddings&lt;br&gt;
Graduations&lt;br&gt;
Partying on a Thursday&lt;br&gt;
DJs who care about music too much&lt;br&gt;
People who never smile finally smiling&lt;br&gt;
Butterflies in stomach&lt;br&gt;
Hands&lt;br&gt;
Listening to a song that you loved when you were younger&lt;br&gt;
Instantly loving a song the first few seconds of listening to it&lt;br&gt;
People doing well&lt;br&gt;
People writing honestly&lt;br&gt;
People being kind&lt;br&gt;
People with robust noses&lt;br&gt;
Dancing until the sun rises at the club&lt;br&gt;
Teaching children math&lt;br&gt;
Being asked for advice&lt;br&gt;
Helping people learn djing/ableton&lt;br&gt;
Showing people my vinyl collection&lt;br&gt;
People complementing me on my photography&lt;br&gt;
Random people DMing and getting coffee&lt;br&gt;
Wholesome interactions on X&lt;br&gt;
Babies&lt;br&gt;
Small animals in the forest&lt;br&gt;
The sound of wolves&lt;br&gt;
Istanbul&lt;br&gt;
Seeing fish swimming in the ocean&lt;br&gt;
Going to strange places&lt;br&gt;
Eating at cheap restaurants with friends&lt;br&gt;
Basement&lt;br&gt;
OHM&lt;br&gt;
Bassiani&lt;br&gt;
TES&lt;br&gt;
Berghain&lt;br&gt;
Public records&lt;br&gt;
Paragon&lt;br&gt;
Mansions&lt;br&gt;
Kosher Chinese food&lt;br&gt;
Backgammon&lt;br&gt;
Golden retrievers&lt;br&gt;
Disco&lt;br&gt;
House music&lt;br&gt;
Black and white photography&lt;br&gt;
Carrot salad&lt;br&gt;
Falafel&lt;br&gt;
The Jordanian restaurant in my neighborhood&lt;br&gt;
Spontaneous trips&lt;br&gt;
My dads humor&lt;br&gt;
My moms kindness&lt;br&gt;
My brothers determination&lt;br&gt;
My mutuals who have been with my since Georgia&lt;br&gt;
Sleepy Sunday mornings&lt;br&gt;
Paper Newspapers&lt;br&gt;
My old iPhone SE&lt;br&gt;
New socks&lt;br&gt;
The Y&lt;br&gt;
Drinking 1 beer&lt;br&gt;
Drinking too many beers&lt;br&gt;
Really dirty martinis&lt;br&gt;
People who find me funny&lt;br&gt;
Snow&lt;br&gt;
Analog electronic music&lt;br&gt;
Redemption arc&lt;br&gt;
Orange wine&lt;br&gt;
Honor&lt;br&gt;
Honesty&lt;br&gt;
Nicotine&lt;br&gt;
High ceilings&lt;br&gt;
Steak&lt;br&gt;
Oysters&lt;br&gt;
Old vice documentaries&lt;br&gt;
The old internet&lt;br&gt;
Painting&lt;br&gt;
Charcoal drawings&lt;br&gt;
Desire&lt;br&gt;
Naps&lt;br&gt;
New England&lt;br&gt;
Montreal&lt;br&gt;
Service works who are nice to me but didn’t need to be&lt;br&gt;
Sushi&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Just do it</title><link>http://localhost:1313/writing/do-things/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 11:23:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/do-things/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;If there&amp;rsquo;s one piece of advice I would give to anyone, it would be this: just do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Modern life has turned most of us into pure consumers. We&amp;rsquo;re on an IV drip of content, constantly scrolling and waiting for the next thing to show up on our screens. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t always like this, but years of optimization have made our phones possibly the most addictive things in the world. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a cure for this phenomenon: you just have to do it.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Georgia</title><link>http://localhost:1313/writing/reflections-on-georgia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:23:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/reflections-on-georgia/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I am back in NYC, in my childhood room, writing this essay. It feels as if the past 6 months were a dream or a hallucination. It all went by so quickly and so slowly, but now it is over. I have such overwhelming love for Tbilisi and the people of Georgia, it almost feels like I have left home to go somewhere new. The air and atmosphere are different in NYC; it&amp;rsquo;s hard to explain, but it feels a bit less serious, a bit more new world-y, as if we are all just making it up as we walk the streets of Brooklyn. New York is also much busier and louder, making the transition a bit more jarring.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>24 Years - Some Reflections</title><link>http://localhost:1313/writing/24-years/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 11:23:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/24-years/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I turned 24 this Sunday and it was a crazy, wonderful, and joyous time in Tbilisi with friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For most of my life there was a mismatch of my perceived age and my biological age. When I was a teenager, I always felt that I was older. Then when covid hit, I felt that I had lost 2 years and that I was younger than I actually was. So I wasn&amp;rsquo;t 23, but 21, and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t graduating but just starting junior year. However, time is unsentimental and hardworking, and I was in fact 23 and I did, in fact, graduate. However, after my time in Georgia, I finally feel my actual age. It&amp;rsquo;s as if two gears lined up just perfectly. My early 20s was wrapped up with great friends, loud music, and spectacular food. Now I am ready to continue the march in my life and build something that I and the people that supported me will be proud of.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Bassiani</title><link>http://localhost:1313/writing/bassiani/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:23:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/bassiani/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Bassiani is a club in Tbilisi. Some say it’s the best techno club in the world. It was founded 9 year ago in the empty swimming pool of the city&amp;rsquo;s soccer stadium. The stadium is a relic of Tbilisi&amp;rsquo;s Soviet past, a gigantic concrete monument to the once-command economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today is the season closing of Bassiani. It&amp;rsquo;s the biggest party in Georgia. All week, every Georgian I&amp;rsquo;ve met has encouraged me to go to this party. Bassiani closes over the summer because most Georgians leave during August and return in September. Therefore, for seven weeks, the Bassiani main room will be closed, only leaving the smaller room open once a week. The party starts on Friday at midnight and continues for 24 hours. I have been advised to arrive in the morning, to beat the rush and see the three Georgian DJs all playing together at midday on Saturday. On Friday, I go to sleep early to prepare my body for the day ahead.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kick Drums and Vsco Girls</title><link>http://localhost:1313/writing/kick-drums-and-vsco-girls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 11:23:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/writing/kick-drums-and-vsco-girls/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="an-examination-of-the-social-scene-economics-of-a-hyper-pop-brooklyn-rave-may-2023"&gt;An examination of the social-scene economics of a Hyper-pop Brooklyn Rave, May 2023&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Preamble&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wrote this for a final paper for SOCI UN3675 Organizing Innovation, a course at Columbia in May of 2023&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Abstract&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is hard to throw a party. It is even harder in New York City. It’s even harder when the party is catering to a niche market. In this paper I examine how one party in Brooklyn, Sksksks, organises its labor force around a system of scene economics to ensure its existence. A complex system of creative networks, friendships, and professional nightlife institutions allow for the party to go on. To start and successfully run a party in New York City, a mixture of madness, charisma, and creativity is required, all of which is present at Sksksks. In this paper, I explore how networks aid in new entrepreneurial endeavours and how this case study can be mapped to more general economic cases. &lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>